You have the spirit of anger.
Yes.
This spirit of anger keeps destroying your home.
Yes, sir.
Take it easy; there is a fast they asked you to do.
You did not do it at all.
Yes, sir.
They asked you to fast for two days.
The prophecy you gave is that I have a spirit of anger.
Because of that, I lock my husband when we are fighting and tear his clothes.
Please, Man of God, deliver me.
I lock my husband and tear his clothes when the spirit comes.
What did I tell you? I said the anger has destroyed your home.
Yes, sir.
Anybody who sees you sees a beautiful woman but you're going through a thorough punishment.
Anger.
Yes, sir; I do cry.
Where is your husband?
My husband is in the church.
- Can you go and call your husband.
- Mr Godwin, come out.
Prophecy Confirmation
Man of God, what you said about my wife is true.
Any time she is fighting with me, she will hold my clothes and hold my penis.
Then I will beg her.
Man of God, please deliver us.
Man of God, help me. She always fights me.
Any time we fight, I will beg her.
She will hold my clothes and tear my clothes; she will not allow me to go out.
And hold your what?
My penis.
Man of God, sometimes he will go out to drink.
When he comes back, I will be angry that he went out.
You can't find any other place to hold.
Prophecy Confirmation
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I want to see you people. It's alright; it's over.
The danger there is that you locked your husband inside and you locked it with the key.
Yes, sir.
For what?
If that anger came, sir - but I know I am free today; it won't happen again.
That is not what I am asking you.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Mrs Godwin Iyan Okoh.
I'm from Ebonyi state; I reside in Osun state.
The person beside me is my husband.
The other ones are my children.
The prophecy the man of God gave to me last Sunday was 100% true.
I had a spirit of anger, just like the man of God said.
That spirit of anger has destroyed my home.
When the spirit came, I would fight my husband.
When we started fighting, I would want my husband to wound me
before I would leave him to go.
When the spirit came over me, I would like to fight my husband,
tear his clothes, his trousers.
I would then hold his manhood so that he would kill me before escaping.
That must have been a very serious spirit of anger.
As the woman said, it nearly destroyed the home.
Can you share with us more of the kind of fighting that occurred between you and your husband.
This fighting started since we got married.
Sometimes, we would fight every week, every month.
When I was still having a child with him, I would fight with him.
When my kids were still small, we would fight.
It is just my two sons that would witness and still recollect how we would fight.
If we wanted to fight, I would look my husband into the room.
I would tell my husband, "If you don't kill me, you are not going anywhere".
My husband would start beating me, hitting me so that he would then escape.
Immediately the spirit left me, I would say, "I will not do that again".
But when the spirit came, I would fight.
It would normally start when he went out to drink.
When he came back, I would start being angry with him.
Ok. You said something that you even used to lock your husband and yourself in the room.
What did you do with the key when you locked the door?
When I locked the door, I would throw the key (away).
Both of us wouldn't find where the key was.
But when he beat me, sometimes, he would just see the key in time.
He might open the door or sometimes, he would use his leg to break the door and run out.
So that was how the spirit of anger had caused this problem and disunity in the home.
Yes. Even when the spirit came and my children were still small, I would beat, hit them.
My second son was even telling me at a certain time, "Mummy, you have changed.
You don't beat us again. You don't play karate again".
During the times you were having this disunity as a result of this spirit of anger
that caused a constant fight between you and your husband,
were there some efforts put in place to bring about settlement between you and your husband
before you finally received your deliverance last week Sunday?
Yes. My husband's mother and family would call us that we should stop fighting;
that this thing we were doing was not good;
that if we continued fighting like this and separated, what would happen to the kids.
My mother-in-law would plead with me that I should calm down.
When my mother-in-law finished talking to me, I would accept.
But when the spirit came again, I would start and not even remember what she said to me again.
That means it was a spirit you could not control as she said that our fight is not carnal
and it was only God that could deliver this family.
That was what happened last week Sunday and it all came through the power of prophecy.
My name is Godwin Iyan Okoh. I'm from Obonyi state.
This is my lovely wife and these are my children.
According to the prophecy of last week - the prophecy is 100% true
because my wife had the spirit of anger.
I myself had the spirit of drinking.
Sometimes, I would go out to drink.
When I came back, my wife wouldn't be happy.
As a man, I would try to tell her that I was the owner of the house;
that she couldn't control me.
From there, we would be fighting.
Sometimes, she would tear my clothes and hold my penis.
She would not allow me to go out.
To the extent, that one day, she locked the door.
I didn't know where she dropped the key.
She said I must kill her.
I then used my leg to break the door.
Sometimes, after begging her, she would open the door.
So this was how the spirit disturbed our marriage.
So let's ask your wife.
How did you normally feel during this time you engaged your husband in those fights?
When the spirit came, I couldn't control myself.
Nobody could tell me something I would accept.
I liked it when the two of us were fighting.
After the fighting, I would say, "Ah, why did I do this?"
I would tell myself, "I will not do this again".
The spirit would still torment me to fight.
But ever since the man of God gave these words of prophecy to you last week Sunday
and went on to deliver you and your husband,
can you tell us the changes you have seen in your life and your marriage?
The spirit has left me; we are living fine.
It is like the first day we met.
Ladies that are here, the first day you met your husband, you know how it is.
Hallelujah. Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
I said, put your hands together for Jesus!
We should give glory to God for this power of prophecy through His anointed one, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
If not for the power of prophecy that revealed the problem in this marriage,
we know, as the woman said, it would have destroyed the home
and we know what the consequences would have been.
And look at the beautiful family we are seeing today.
They would not have been here today to share this wonderful testimony
with the children of God, if not for the power of prophecy.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Since last week, it is as if we just wedded.
Since then, she has changed.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Hallelujah. Once again, put your hands together for Jesus!
You also talked about the spirit of drinking.
Ever since you received your deliverance, what can you say concerning that?
My sister, in fact, before, every day I had to drink something - like 3-4 bottles in a day.
But since last Sunday - even the church I was going to before at my place,
I would be in the church and pretend as if I was going to urinate.
I would take (a drink) but now, that spirit has left me - the spirit of drinking.
What kind of drink did you use to take then?
My sister, we have many people here that were drinking before.
We have different types of drinks in the town - alcohol.
So we have just heard from our brother that he was into this drinking of alcohol
and he took many bottles in a day.
But not only was peace restored into the marriage,
he was also delivered from that spirit of drinking - drunkenness.
And since that deliverance last week Sunday, it is a week now.
Have you ever tasted alcohol?
No, I have not.
So ever since your deliverance, do you still have that urge to drink?
Not at all.
Hallelujah. We give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful deliverance
that has taken place in this family.
My name is Uchechukwu Iyan.
I'm the first son of Mr Godwin - my parents.
Back then, it used to be terrible.
Every time they started fighting, all our neighbours used to come around.
It was always very terrible.
Our landlord would have to call to speak to them.
Some nights, my dad wouldn't sleep at home.
He would go out to drink and after the fight like that, he would just leave.
But now, everything has changed; there is peace in the family right now.
We are hearing from the children themselves. Put your hands together for Jesus!
My name is Iyan Uchechukwu.
These are my brothers and those are my parents.
I can confirm the prophecy that the man of God gave to my mother about anger.
When I was very young, I remember vividly that one day, my dad just came back home,
took the television set and smashed it on the floor - just like that.
I think it was because they quarrelled in the morning.
So all these things were going on and it was embarrassing for us.
Like going to school, our parents were always fighting and all these kinds of things.
I thank God that after last week, everything has been okay
and there has been peace in the family.
I give glory to God. Emmanuel!
Mr & Mrs Godwin Iyan Okoh & Family
Prophecy Testimony
The word of advice I have for the whole world:
Please, those who have this kind of problem - trust in God.
God will see you through one day.
Continue praying; don't leave God, in Jesus' name.
The word of advice I have for the world is:
If you are having any problem, just have faith in God.
One day, God will see you through as He has seen my family through, in Jesus' name.
So you have heard a word of advice from the couple,
advising all to have faith in God.
Whatever problem you may be having, God is more than able to see you through.
We give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful thing He has done in your family -
for this restoration of peace, harmony and unity in the family.
We just want to advise you that you should make sure
you continue to stay true to our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ
and make His Word the standard for your life
and we know that better is not good enough, the best is always yet to come.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
TT: Mel Flowers 12/01/2019
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 12/01/2019